RESUME

Yousuf Jahangir Shaik Mohammed

Email: <u>yousufja@gmail.com</u> Website: <u>https://yousufja.com/</u>

Skills: Networking, Routing (BGP, OSPF, EIGRP, RIP), Ethernet (VLANs, STP, VTP, DTP, VRRP, HSRP, GLBP) Linux, Windows Server, Cloud Computing, Microsoft Azure, Google Cloud Platform, Tech/IT Support and Customer Service

Certifications: CCNA, CCNP, RHCE

Summary:

5+ months of Experience as a Systems/Network Administrator (India).

7+ months of experience as a customer service agent (chat process) in Amazon (India).

4 years 1 month of experience as Seller Support Associate in Amazon. On Feb 19, 2018, I moved to T4, where my job role was to triage seller support tickets for the Dev teams and make process improvements (India).

Previous Work Experience:

2012 – 2013: System/Network Administrator – MSSI Pvt Ltd.

 Assistant System/Network Administrator for Materials Software System India Pvt. Ltd. from 24-12-2012 to 15-06-2013(5 months)

Job Description:

- Deploying and maintaining Windows Server 2003 active directory services.
- Configured and managed Manageable Dlink switch, CISCO 2960 switch and Fortinet fortigate firewall.
- Troubleshooting all the Desktop related issues to server related issues.
- Maintaining CentOS server with CVS server and a syslog server.
- Assisted in deploying a website on Amazon web services with SSL.

CERTIFICATIONS OBTAINED:

- RHCE (Red Hat Certified Engineer in RHEL 6.0). (Cert no. 111-160-685)
- Attempted CCIE(R&S) LAB on 23-07-2015
- CCIE routing and switching written on 21-03-2015.
- CCNP (Cisco Certified Network Professional in Routing and Switching). (2011)

- CCNA Security (2011)
- CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate in Routing and Switching) (2010)
- My Cisco certs have expired; however, I can recertify them if that is a requirement.

Programming/Scripting Skills:

- Python
- Bash
- C++

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:

- Computer Information Technology Diploma, Lethbridge College (Sep 2021 Apr 2023) with 3.58 GPA.
- Bachelors in information technology from Sikkim Manipal University (India). Secured 65% in the year 2016.

Other Employment details:

March 2022 - Present: Night Grocery Clerk at Real Canadian Superstore

April 2023 - Present: Night Driver at Neuron Mobility

<u>2017 – 2021</u>: Seller Support Associate (L3) – Amazon.com

- Worked as a Seller Support Associate (Email process) for Amazon.com from January 23, 2017.
- Moved to T4(Trouble Tickets Triage Team) on Feb 19, 2018, where my job role was to triage seller support tickets raised by the associates to the Dev teams, also my role required diving on the tickets to bridge the process gaps.

2013 - 2014: Customer Service Associate (L2) - Amazon.com

Customer service associate (chat process) for Amazon.com from 25-07-2013 to 03-06-2014 (7 months)